bankit.in 2019-07-22

# 

## PRIVACY POLICY

BANKIT is committed to respect privacy and choice of its User(s) and /or business associates while using this website. This statement highlights our privacy practices regarding Personal Information that we hold of our User and business associates.

#### Definition:

For the purposes of this privacy policy, ‘Personal Information’ means and includes all information that can be linked to a specific individual or to identify any individual, such as name, address, mailing address, telephone number, email ID, credit card details, Debit card details, cardholder name, card expiration date, information about User mobile phone, DTH service, data card, electricity connection and any details that may have been voluntarily provided by the User in connection with availing any of the services on this site. Exception: Any information which User provides to an open, public environment or forum including (without limitation) any blog, chat room, social networking site, albums, community, classifieds or discussion board, is not confidential, does not constitute Personal Information, and is not subject to protection under Privacy Policy.

#### Use of Personal Information:

BANKIT uses personal information for providing User with services explicitly requested by the User, to resolve disputes, troubleshoot concerns, for promoting safe services, collect money, assess User’s interest in our services, inform User about offers, services, updates, customize User’s experience, detect & protect BANKIT against error, fraud and other criminal activity, enforce our terms and conditions, etc.

#### Disclosure of Data / Information:

BANKIT will not share any personal or sensitive data with any external organization unless the same is necessary to enable it to provide services (to User or business associates) or to enable completion of a legitimate transaction or for reporting which may be necessary or required pursuant to applicable law or pursuant to the terms and conditions applicable to such information as agreed to with BANKIT. BANKIT may disclose information about User and / or business associates as permitted or required by law.

#### Observation of reasonable security practices:

BANKIT shall take all reasonable precautions to maintain the confidentiality of personal and sensitive information / data pertaining to its User and business associates by imparting proper training to its employees and by providing restricted access to persons who may require access to such data strictly on a need to know basis.

#### Links to Other Websites:

Website contains links to other websites. Please note that when User click on one of these links, User enters into another website for which BANKIT has no responsibility. BANKIT encourage User to read the privacy statements of all such sites as their policies may be materially different from this Privacy Policy. User is solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of its passwords and other membership account information.

#### Updates to this Privacy Policy:

BANKIT may change the data privacy practices and update this privacy statement as and when the need arises, and the same shall be made available on the website.
